[{"answer": "Hey, what's going on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "New couch? Why", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What are you doing with your old couch", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah, I'll take it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Right there, guys. That's perfect. Ah? Whatta ya think, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh no, I don't want anyone sitting on it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well...Poppie. I think differently", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "The that place gives me the right to do that! Let's go my friend, c'mon", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Do you know that I have been using the same bottle of shampoo for a year? And I shampoo every day.  So, what do you think of my conversation", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You don't have any furniture", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'd like to rent Breakfast At that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Out? Oh no, I've been to four other places, you're the only ones that have had it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "So long. I'll see you tonight", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What is what", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What is what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What puddle", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "This puddle on my sofa", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "That puddle!", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, what is it then?! My new sofa! Poppie peed on my new sofa", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't care if it comes out, I can't sit on that anymore", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hi.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh, I missed you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I think about you all the time", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Do you think about me", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "But that's the idea, you make your own pie", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What gives you the right to tell me how I would make my pie", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Couch.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It's not your seat", "qsentId": 28}]